<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Forty</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Forty</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Photography</title>
      <link>/projects/photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/photography/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I take pictures. This project is about the pictures I take. Sometimes, they are pictures of cats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design</title>
      <link>/projects/design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/design/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing</title>
      <link>/projects/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/writing/</guid>
      <description>Aromatic aroma con panna, crema so coffee robust coffee barista, café au lait trifecta that strong blue mountain cortado aftertaste. Aroma extraction french press, skinny sweet, blue mountain cup roast barista, beans, extra cappuccino mug crema strong.
To go viennese cream to go, flavour, so mocha as, carajillo iced et a siphon froth. Aged, eu, cup, brewed aroma kopi-luwak, coffee, id viennese french press brewed grounds acerbic froth. Decaffeinated acerbic, spoon beans seasonal, french press café au lait mazagran roast chicory, pumpkin spice galão as fair trade, dark irish cup ristretto half and half whipped shop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>詹姆斯·哈登</title>
      <link>/post/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>基本资料： 詹姆斯·哈登（James Harden），1989年8月26日出生于美国加利福尼亚州洛杉矶（ Los Angeles, California），美国职业篮球运动员，司职后卫，效力于NBA休斯顿火箭队。 詹姆斯·哈登于2009年通过选秀进入NBA，先后效力于雷霆队和火箭队，新秀赛季入选最佳新秀第二阵容，2011-12赛季当选最佳第六人，3次入选最佳阵容第一阵容，5次入选全明星阵容。 詹姆斯·哈登于2012年随美国男篮获伦敦奥运会金牌，2014年随美国队获西班牙篮球世界杯冠军。
高中时期 2003年夏，詹姆斯·哈登进入位于洛杉矶西南部郊区的莱克伍德阿迪西亚高中读书。 哈登身体发育得较晚，进入高中时只有1米85，还不会扣篮，只能苦练基本功和底角三分球。高一时，哈登场均可得13.2分。 等到哈登高二读到一半，他的身高又长了几英寸，各项技能逐渐被开发出来。哈登高二场均可得18.8分、7.7个篮板和3.5次助攻。 高三、高四时，哈登作为绝对主力，带领校队分别取得取得33胜1负和33胜2负的战绩，连续两年拿下了加州高中联赛的冠军。哈登入选了全美高中全明星阵容。 哈登高四临近毕业时，NCAA众多豪门开始登门造访，试图说服哈登加盟，包括哈登的偶像卡波诺曾效力过的加州大学洛杉矶分校，但哈登却出人意料地选择了亚利桑那州立大学，唯一原因是哈登的高中教练斯科特·佩拉成为了亚利桑那州大的助教。
大学时期 大一赛季，詹姆斯·哈登场均贡献17.8分以及赛区最高的73次抢断，帮助亚利桑那州大拿到了21胜13负的战绩。哈登还登上了《体育画报》的封面。 大学时期 大学时期 大二赛季，哈登场均可得20.1分5.6个篮板4.2次助攻，命中率达到了50%。在1995年之后，只有5名大学球员能有这种全能数据，其中包括韦德和布兰顿·罗伊。此外，这一赛季哈登共270次走上了罚球线，平均每场将获得7.6次罚球机会。亚利桑那州大打出了25胜10负的战绩，一举压倒了死敌亚利桑那大学的21胜14负，成功进入NCAA锦标赛。虽然第二轮便被锡拉丘兹大学淘汰出局，但当赛季哈登还是拿到了太平洋十区年度最佳球员。
The Home Page The home page, or landing page, is the first page that many visitors to a site see. It is the index.html file in the root directory of the web site. Since Hugo writes files to the public/ directory, our home page is public/index.html.
Site Configuration File When Hugo runs, it looks for a configuration file that contains settings that override default values for the entire site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>斯蒂芬·库里</title>
      <link>/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>顾客都会看到好吃的客户客户端客户端还是看好款式的好看 ▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.
Create your Hugo configuration file Hugo can read your configuration as JSON, YAML or TOML. Hugo supports parameters custom configuration too. Refer to the Hugo configuration documentation for details.
Set your configuration publish folder to _site The default is for Jekyll to publish to _site and for Hugo to publish to public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Ipsum</title>
      <link>/blog/coffee-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:04:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/coffee-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>Aromatic aroma con panna, crema so coffee robust coffee barista, café au lait trifecta that strong blue mountain cortado aftertaste. Aroma extraction french press, skinny sweet, blue mountain cup roast barista, beans, extra cappuccino mug crema strong. Americano caffeine white, con panna saucer sit, con panna eu, carajillo aftertaste kopi-luwak, body aftertaste cup single origin café au lait saucer. Macchiato java sweet arabica, turkish cup, eu flavour mug extraction white cortado saucer est white brewed instant, rich, barista breve cappuccino barista organic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Ipsum</title>
      <link>/blog/startup-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:04:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/startup-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>SpaceTeam affordances quantitative vs. qualitative SpaceTeam physical computing earned media thinker-maker-doer pair programming. Bootstrapping pitch deck physical computing driven cortado human-centered design innovate human-centered design driven. Grok pitch deck fund pitch deck sticky note affordances minimum viable product integrate paradigm viral iterate. Driven fund thought leader personas workflow SpaceTeam viral pair programming physical computing intuitive 360 campaign latte bootstrapping minimum viable product. Bootstrapping physical computing responsive pitch deck SpaceTeam parallax long shadow pitch deck bootstrapping ideate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>斯蒂芬·库里</title>
      <link>/blogs/aliquam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:42:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/aliquam/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>詹姆斯·哈登</title>
      <link>/blogs/tempus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/tempus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>拉塞尔·维斯布鲁克</title>
      <link>/blogs/magna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/magna/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>凯里·欧文</title>
      <link>/blogs/ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/ipsum/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 13:23:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>In the Contact section of Introduction, you may optionally display the current time in your preferred timezone.
This lets visitors know what sort of response time to expect when they contact you. The timezone is easily set in the config file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 13:19:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description> This is Introduction, a minimal scrolling website theme made for Hugo.
Features  Responsive display on any size screen Smooth fade-in on load with CSS3 Smooth scrolling to page sections from navigation Light and Dark themes Projects section with any number of projects: configurable as a photo gallery, popup with details, or external links Blog section with optionally included Latest Post, on the main page or as a separate section Styled Markdown throughout with support for HighlightJS  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>拉塞尔·维斯布鲁克</title>
      <link>/post/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>郎佐·鲍尔</title>
      <link>/post/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>